[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e13"
  },
  "name": "My first deck",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Nothing",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a66bd334ed16dc4e0d",
  "public": true,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "I am a new user",
      "back": "How may I help you?"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is my favorite color?",
      "back": "Blue!"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is ChatGPT",
      "back": "A chatbot that can answer questions with good prompts"
    },
    {
      "front": "What does the fox say?",
      "back": "Go back to 2013"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is 2+2+2+2?",
      "back": "It is 8"
    },
    {
      "front": "How many raw eggs do I consume on a daily basis?",
      "back": "More than 0"
    },
    {
      "front": "Who is the best professor",
      "back": "Patrick Hill"
    },
    {
      "front": "What CPU powered the Samsung Galaxy S6",
      "back": "Samsung Exynos 7420"
    },
    {
      "front": "Jesse",
      "back": "Pinkman"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e14"
  },
  "name": "Song lyrics",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Songs I like",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a66bd334ed16dc4e0d",
  "public": true,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Everything you say to me",
      "back": "Takes me one step closer to the edge, and I'm about to break"
    },
    {
      "front": "Shot down in daylight",
      "back": "My bullets are songs on the radio"
    },
    {
      "front": "So thank you, for coming to my birthday party",
      "back": "I'm one minute old today"
    },
    {
      "front": "The voices in my head keep on telling me I'm cursed",
      "back": "I'm paranoid, I don't wanna make it any worse"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e15"
  },
  "name": "An",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Rhymes",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a66bd334ed16dc4e0d",
  "public": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Man",
      "back": "Woman"
    },
    {
      "front": "Bran",
      "back": "Muffin"
    },
    {
      "front": "Toucan",
      "back": "Sam"
    },
    {
      "front": "Tan",
      "back": "sine/cosine"
    },
    {
      "front": "Dan",
      "back": "Craig"
    },
    {
      "front": "Gan",
      "back": "356 M"
    },
    {
      "front": "Pan",
      "back": "Potts"
    },
    {
      "front": "Jan",
      "back": "uary"
    },
    {
      "front": "NaN",
      "back": "Not a number"
    },
    {
      "front": "Iran",
      "back": "A country in the middle east"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e16"
  },
  "name": "Another first deck",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "shorts",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a66bd334ed16dc4e0d",
  "public": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Heat waves",
      "back": "Be fakin me out"
    },
    {
      "front": "Wellsley farms",
      "back": "Tavern blend"
    },
    {
      "front": "Water freezes at: ",
      "back": "32 degrees F"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is a segmentation fault",
      "back": "When you do something illegal with pointers"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e17"
  },
  "name": "User2 private dek",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "more stuff",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a76bd334ed16dc4e0e",
  "public": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Are ionic or colavent bonds stronger?",
      "back": "covalent"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is the best programming language?",
      "back": "Javascript"
    },
    {
      "front": "Who is my idol",
      "back": "The American one"
    },
    {
      "front": "What will the Turing machine do?",
      "back": "M1 will"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is the composiiton of water?",
      "back": "H20"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is John's favorite color",
      "back": "purple"
    },
    {
      "front": "To be?",
      "back": "Or not to be?"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is the meaning of life?",
      "back": "Being happy (?)"
    },
    {
      "front": "Who is the best web developer?",
      "back": "A spider. They've been doing it for years"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e18"
  },
  "name": "Science things",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Science",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a76bd334ed16dc4e0e",
  "public": true,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Wax, grease, fat",
      "back": "Lipids"
    },
    {
      "front": "Hypothesis",
      "back": "Something that you want to test for if it's true"
    },
    {
      "front": "What was Albert's last name?",
      "back": "Einstein"
    },
    {
      "front": "What country did a lot of cool math stuff?",
      "back": "Greece, probably"
    },
    {
      "front": "Safest way to smell chemicals in a lab?",
      "back": "Waft the fumes from over the beaker. Do not sniff directly"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e19"
  },
  "name": "About Daniel",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Random Trivia",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a76bd334ed16dc4e0f",
  "public": true,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What phone do I have?",
      "back": "Samsung Galaxy S10 plus"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is my favorite car and color?",
      "back": "Subaru WRX. World rally blue"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is my favorite programming language?",
      "back": "Python"
    },
    {
      "front": "What month was I born in",
      "back": "January"
    },
    {
      "front": "I have been out of the country before",
      "back": "True"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is my favorite show?",
      "back": "Helluva Boss"
    },
    {
      "front": "How tall am I?",
      "back": "6 big ol' American feet tall"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is my best time for solving a rubik's cube?",
      "back": "31 seconds"
    },
    {
      "front": "What day did I get my Eagle Scout Award?",
      "back": "January 17, 2019"
    },
    {
      "front": "Programming languages I know",
      "back": "Java, Python, Javascript, C, C++, C#, Bash, SQL, OCaml, HTML, Scheme, LaTeX"
    },
    {
      "front": "Favorite obscure band",
      "back": "New Politics"
    },
    {
      "front": "Game with most hours",
      "back": "Terraria"
    },
    {
      "front": "My smash bros main",
      "back": "ROB"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e1a"
  },
  "name": "Songs 1",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Songs I like",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a76bd334ed16dc4e0f",
  "public": true,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "New Politics",
      "back": "CIA, One of Us"
    },
    {
      "front": "Falling in Reverse",
      "back": "Popular Monster, Voices in my head, Zombified"
    },
    {
      "front": "All Time Low",
      "back": "A Love Like War"
    },
    {
      "front": "Fall Out Boy",
      "back": "Centuries, Thnks fr th Mmrs, Light Em Up"
    },
    {
      "front": "The Offspring",
      "back": "Let The Bad Times Roll, The Kids Aren't Alright, Self Esteem"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e1b"
  },
  "name": "Songs 2",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Songs I like",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a76bd334ed16dc4e0f",
  "public": true,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Panic! At the Disco",
      "back": "High Hopes, Saturday Night"
    },
    {
      "front": "Fister the People",
      "back": "Sit Next to me"
    },
    {
      "front": "Twenty One Pilots",
      "back": "Stressed Out, Lane Boy"
    },
    {
      "front": "AJR",
      "back": "100 Bad Days, Birthday Party"
    },
    {
      "front": "Glass Animals",
      "back": "Heat Waves"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e1c"
  },
  "name": "Stevens Classes",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Academics",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a76bd334ed16dc4e0f",
  "public": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "CS 115",
      "back": "Intro to Computer Science"
    },
    {
      "front": "CS 284",
      "back": "Data Structures"
    },
    {
      "front": "CS 385",
      "back": "Algorithms"
    },
    {
      "front": "CS 392",
      "back": "Systems Programming"
    },
    {
      "front": "CS 334",
      "back": "Theory of Computation"
    },
    {
      "front": "CS 516",
      "back": "Compiler Design and Implementation"
    },
    {
      "front": "CS 492",
      "back": "Operating Systems"
    },
    {
      "front": "CS 677",
      "back": "Parallel Programming for many-core processors"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e1d"
  },
  "name": "Long deck 1",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "pants",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a76bd334ed16dc4e0f",
  "public": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "01",
      "back": "AB"
    },
    {
      "front": "CD",
      "back": "EF"
    },
    {
      "front": "GH",
      "back": "IJ"
    },
    {
      "front": "KL",
      "back": "MN"
    },
    {
      "front": "OP",
      "back": "QR"
    },
    {
      "front": "ST",
      "back": "UV"
    },
    {
      "front": "WX",
      "back": "YZ"
    },
    {
      "front": "Hydrogen peroxide",
      "back": "H2O2"
    },
    {
      "front": "Yankees",
      "back": "Baseball"
    },
    {
      "front": "Owen Wilson",
      "back": "Lightning McQueen"
    },
    {
      "front": "Edward Norton",
      "back": "Deranged, disturbed character"
    },
    {
      "front": "Daniel Craig",
      "back": "James Bond, Knives Out"
    },
    {
      "front": "Acorn",
      "back": "Oak tree"
    },
    {
      "front": "Engine in 4th gen WRX",
      "back": "FA20DIT turbocharged 2.0L Boxer 4 cylinder"
    },
    {
      "front": "Best snake",
      "back": "Python"
    },
    {
      "front": "Am I an enthusiast?",
      "back": "True"
    },
    {
      "front": "Do I watch anime?",
      "back": "No"
    },
    {
      "front": "Favorite cheap food",
      "back": "Spicy ramen"
    },
    {
      "front": "Amdahl's law",
      "back": "The amount of gain you can get from parallelizing a workload where a certain percentage is parallelizable"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is my code for a one line leetcode solution?",
      "back": "return len(list(filter(lambda x:x=='1',str(format(n,'b')))))"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e1e"
  },
  "name": "Short deck 1",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "shorts",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a76bd334ed16dc4e0f",
  "public": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Batman",
      "back": "Robin"
    },
    {
      "front": "Rubik's",
      "back": "cube"
    },
    {
      "front": "Peanut Butter",
      "back": "Jelly"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e1f"
  },
  "name": "Car facts",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Random Trivia",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a76bd334ed16dc4e0f",
  "public": true,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Is the Honda V6 a single or dual overhead cam?",
      "back": "Single overhead camshaft"
    },
    {
      "front": "What was the first model year of the mustang?",
      "back": "1964"
    },
    {
      "front": "Displacement of the Gm 5 cylinder?",
      "back": "3.7 Liters"
    },
    {
      "front": "What engine layout is used in FWD cars?",
      "back": "Transverse. The engine is turned sideways to spin the front wheels."
    },
    {
      "front": "Name the 4 engine strokes",
      "back": "Intake, compression, power, exhaust"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is the redline on the Honda S2000?",
      "back": "9000 RPM for the first generation, and 8300 RPM for the second"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e20"
  },
  "name": "Places I've been",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "About me",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a76bd334ed16dc4e0f",
  "public": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "United States",
      "back": "NJ, NY, FL, UT, CA, PA, MD"
    },
    {
      "front": "Europe",
      "back": "Italy, France, Spain"
    },
    {
      "front": "Caribbean",
      "back": "Jamaica, Puerto Rico, St. Thomas, St. Maarten, St. Lucia, Barbados, Bermuda"
    },
    {
      "front": "Mexico",
      "back": "Cozumel, Xcaret"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e21"
  },
  "name": "Helluva Nonsense",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Random Trivia",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a76bd334ed16dc4e10",
  "public": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Moxxie's wife",
      "back": "Millie"
    },
    {
      "front": "Who does Stolas hate the most?",
      "back": "Stella"
    },
    {
      "front": "Is Moxxie and Millie's relationship healthy?",
      "back": "YES"
    },
    {
      "front": "What episode did Moxxie wear a dress?",
      "back": "Episode 6"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is one thing Moxxie likes?",
      "back": "Musical theater"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e22"
  },
  "name": "Helluva Boss Members",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Random Trivia",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a76bd334ed16dc4e10",
  "public": true,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Vivienne Medrano",
      "back": "Producer"
    },
    {
      "front": "Brandon Rogers",
      "back": "Blitzo"
    },
    {
      "front": "Erica Lindbeck",
      "back": "Loona"
    },
    {
      "front": "Richard Horvitz",
      "back": "Moxxie"
    },
    {
      "front": "Norman Reedus",
      "back": "Striker"
    },
    {
      "front": "Vivian Nixon",
      "back": "Millie"
    },
    {
      "front": "Bryce Pinkham",
      "back": "Stolas"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e23"
  },
  "name": "Aggretsuko facts",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Random Trivia",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e11",
  "public": true,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What does Aggretsuko mean?",
      "back": "It means aggresive Retsuko. Rage"
    },
    {
      "front": "Who is Retsuko's boss?",
      "back": "Mr. Ton"
    },
    {
      "front": "What device does Mr. Ton use?",
      "back": "Abacus"
    },
    {
      "front": "How many boyfriends has Retsuko had?",
      "back": "Two boyfriends"
    },
    {
      "front": "Who is Retsuko's not-so-secret admirer?",
      "back": "Haida"
    },
    {
      "front": "What is Retsuko's 'secret' trait?",
      "back": "Being a hardcore rockstar"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e24"
  },
  "name": "Other stuff",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Misc",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e11",
  "public": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Main plot of first episode?",
      "back": "She wore crocs to work"
    },
    {
      "front": "What company made Aggretsuko?",
      "back": "Sanrio"
    },
    {
      "front": "How old is Retsuko?",
      "back": "25 years old"
    },
    {
      "front": "Is Retsuko okay with being unmarried?",
      "back": "False"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e25"
  },
  "name": "I can't decide",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Nothing",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e12",
  "public": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Muffin",
      "back": "Blueberry or chocolate chip?"
    },
    {
      "front": "Soulmate",
      "back": "Eleanor Shellstrop"
    },
    {
      "front": "Air conditioner",
      "back": "Falls from second story window"
    },
    {
      "front": "Trolley problem",
      "back": "Could not decide"
    },
    {
      "front": "The Good Place",
      "back": "The Bad Place"
    }
  ]
},{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e26"
  },
  "name": "Empty Deck",
  "dateCreated": "12/18/2022",
  "subject": "Nothing",
  "creatorId": "639fd9a86bd334ed16dc4e12",
  "public": true,
  "cards": []
}]